const starWarsQuizData = [
    {
        QuizName: "Star Wars"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "1",
        Question: "What are the force sensitive beings in the Star Wars universe called?",
        Options: ["Mandalorion", "Jedi", "Wookie", "Jawa"],
        Answer: "Jedi"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "2",
        Question: "Which of these is a race in Star Wars?",
        Options: ["Yuzzum", "Salt Vampire", "Gorn", "Talosian"],
        Answer: "Yuzzum"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "3",
        Question: "What race is Yoda?",
        Options: ["Ithorian", "Trandoshan", "Neimoidian", "Unknown"],
        Answer: "Unknown"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "4",
        Question: "What type of ship do the Rebels use during their attempt to destroy the first Death Star?",
        Options: ["U-wing", "Y-wing", "X-wing", "B-wing"],
        Answer: "X-wing"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "5",
        Question: "What order is given by Emperor Palpatine in Revenge of the Sith?",
        Options: ["66", "52", "99", "45"],
        Answer: "66"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "6",
        Question: "What planet does Luke find Yoda on?",
        Options: ["Tatooine", "Yavin 4", "Kashyyk", "Dagobah"],
        Answer: "Dagobah"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "7",
        Question: "Who is the Weequay pirate that is shown prominently in the Clone Wars?",
        Options: ["Cad Bane", "Asajj Ventress", "Shaak Ti", "Hondo Ohnaka"],
        Answer: "Hondo Ohnaka"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "8",
        Question: "Luke had a secret sister that wasn't known until Return of the Jedi. Who was she?",
        Options: ["Padm√©", "Bo-Katan", "Leia", "Ahsoka"],
        Answer: "Leia"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "9",
        Question: "Which planet was destroyed by the Death Star?",
        Options: ["Alderaan", "Hoth", "Bespin", "Mustafar"],
        Answer: "Alderaan"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "10",
        Question: "Who is Lando's co-pilot in Return of the Jedi?",
        Options: ["Greedo", "Nien Nunb", "Hera Syndulla", "Maz kanata"],
        Answer: "Nien Nunb"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "11",
        Question: "What is the name of Jango's, and later, Boba's ship?",
        Options: ["Executor", "Home One", "Slave 1", "Invisible Hand"],
        Answer: "Slave 1"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "12",
        Question: "What species are the guards in Jabba's Palace?",
        Options: ["Bothan", "Duros", "Er'Kit", "Gamorrean"],
        Answer: "Gamorrean"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "13",
        Question: "What color is Yoda?",
        Options: ["Green", "Blue", "Red", "Pink"],
        Answer: "Green"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "14",
        Question: "Han Solo famously likes to state that the Millenium Falcon made the Kessel run in less than how many parsecs?",
        Options: ["12", "10", "5", "7"],
        Answer: "12"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "15",
        Question: "Which hand does Luke lose when fighting Darth Vader?",
        Options: ["Neither", "Left", "Both", "Right"],
        Answer: "Right"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "16",
        Question: "What planet is Rey living on at the beginning of The Force Awakens?",
        Options: ["Tatooine", "Hoth", "Jakku", "Ryloth"],
        Answer: "Jakku"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "17",
        Question: "What two legged creatures are ridden by Rebels in Empire Strikes Back?",
        Options: ["Tauntaun", "Bantha", "Rancor", "Dewback"],
        Answer: "Tauntaun"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "18",
        Question: "Who is the Ewok that befriends Leia on Endor?",
        Options: ["Nippet", "Teebo", "Wicket", "Logray"],
        Answer: "Wicket"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "19",
        Question: "Who is the sarcastic droid that features in Rogue One?",
        Options: ["BB-8", "K-2SO", "AP-5", "4-LOM"],
        Answer: "K-2SO"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "20",
        Question: "Which character is often seen by Jabba's side?",
        Options: ["Pondo Babba", "Salacious B Crumb", "Dr. Cornelious Evazan", "Hem Dazon"],
        Answer: "Salacious B Crumb"
    }
]